Hello, my name is Yuna Shibata.
It's been a while since I wanted to play basketball.
I had a lot of ex-basketball team members and others gather today!
Come here.
Let's enjoy playing basketball together today!
Hey everyone.
How long have you been playing basketball?
Yes, Teresa Ikeda played basketball in junior high and high school.
That's quite a long time!
It looks like 6 years, but it's more like 5 years.
No, I've been playing a lot, but still...
I've been playing for about six years.
She has cool feet, doesn't she?
It's the feet.
One person's color is different from everyone else's.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Let's see.
Satsuki Sugawara's been here about two months.
Why?
She quit right away.
It was like, "Let's see what you can do.
I played minibus in elementary school.
You played minibus?
A year and a half?
I don't think I played for two years.
But I like the Chiba Jets. I go to their games.
I watch them.
So when I see them, I want to play.
I see.
I feel like I'm in the third year of junior high school.
I feel like a junior high school senior.
I was already doing track and field in the first grade.
Running.
Running, running, running outside forever.
I'm the same.
I did it for three years.
It's really like two years.
I didn't really do anything else for a year. I really haven't done anything else for a year.
Offense is so bad at the conversation table
I'm not allowed to participate.
The team is working so hard on offense.
And when you score that many goals, you have to say, "Go for it!" I have to say, "Go for it!
What about you, Mie?
I've never done anything.
Who's that?
I've never heard of him.
I haven't done anything.
But I like her.
Cute.
Mie-chan...
I thought I'd like to do it, so I came.
Now that we know a little bit about everyone's background
Let's start with warming up.
Great.
Who wants to go first?
Bol.
Bol?
There's already...
Hey, Ike.
My foot's in it.
Ike-chan!
No, Yari-chan!
Hang in there.
Ike-chan.
Ikechan.
Ike-da.
Ike!
Ike
ah~ great
Nice try.
Wow, he's so cool!
That's the guy who's doing it.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
I give up. I give up.
I can do it. I can do it.
Quick, quick, quick.
I knew it.
Nice.
I got three.
Quick, quick, quick.
I knew it.
Nice.
Let's fight
Let's fight. That's a good word.
Hey.
Thank you.
Hey, Yuna.
She's flapping her wings.
Flapping wings.
It's flapping its wings.
Here we go.
Fight.
Fight. Fight.
Wow!
This is it.
Yes!
Fight.
This, this, this.
Wow.
Go for it!
I'm in. I'm in. I'm in.
I'm in, I'm in, I'm in.
Wow.
Oh, my God. Go!
Go!
that
I don't know, right?
Griffin.
Oh, you're good!
It's good!
You're good.
Rin, you can do anything.
You can do anything.
That's great.
This, this, this.
I thought we could have a little showdown.
Oh, great.
Guru-bat.
What's this?
Baseball?
It's a baseball bat.
You're writing too much.
I'd like to have a little showdown with a baseball bat.
We'd like you to go around with the bat and shoot at the goal.
First one to say it wins.
How many times do you want to go around?
Five.
About seven.
Between five and ten.
Five might be okay for everyone.
Five is a little low.
Can we go after breakfast?
Come on.
All right.
Let's go.
Come on!
Ikeda.
How many rounds are you doing now?
Three and a half. 3 1/2 periods of time.
How many times now I
Five.
Ikeda, you have two more.
Two more times is enough.
I'm such a screw-up.
You're right.
It's hard to do.
But...
Go, go, go, go.
Ikeda, one more time.
One more.
Go, go, go, go!
Go, go, go.
Whoa! I'm in!
What? It's in!
Come on, Heavenly Father!
Come on!
I can do it! I can do it!
Whoo!
Here we go!
Oh, reverse.
Reverse.
Wait a minute.
Go for it!
How many times are you going to do that, Nao-chan?
I'm going to hit the scorch.
Five, I knew it!
The bat's spinning.
Oh, no, no, no!
Five, Naoi-chan!
It's okay, Naoi-chan, it's okay.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Go for it!
Second win.
Come on. good luck!
go, go, go!
touch me!
go!
I'm scared!
I'm so scared!
Sacchan rebound
Oh, let's get out
Nope
Let's go, let's go, let's go
It's okay, Satchan, it's okay.
Sachan, go, Sachan, go!
Go, go, go, go!
Satchan, go!
Wow!
Okay, start!
What shall I do?
Oh, no, no, no!
Three...
Four.
Oh, my God.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
One second.
Kakki, Kakki, Kakki.
Oh, it looks totally fine.
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
Next.
Come on.
Wait a minute.
Kakki.
Kakki. Kakki.
A little turn. I went around a little bit.
A little turn.
Kakki, it's not turning.
Are you okay?
Two. Two.
Three.
It's Kakki. It's Kakki.
What? What kind of Direction?
Wait a minute. Kakki.
Kakki's in trouble. Kakki's already down.
Are you okay? - No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Stop, stop, stop, stop.
Stop, stop, stop.
Okay, I'd like to end with a 343.
What do you think? How confident are you?
I'm taller than you.
Sure, if you're taller, you'll live.
Height doesn't matter.
I have long arms.
That's where we'll do it.
Okay, here we go.
Here we go.
I don't know.
Joon-hwa, run.
Joon-hwa, cover.
Okay, Sacchan!
Go, Sachan!
I got it.
Matsuo, you're in!
Yay!
Let me in!
Nao-chan!
Wow!
re.
AHHHHH!
ohhhhhhhhhh, I hung up. Ahhhhhh, I hung up.
Pan war
me
Huh!
I'm in, I'm in, I'm in
I'm in.
I'll give you a sign.
I'm in. I'm in.
You're gonna signal?
Oh, no.
Oh!
Saw-chan!
Get in!
Reach.
Match point
Oh, no!
Sou-chan
That's good!
I'm tired
It's fun!
Oh no, oh no, oh no!
I got Suluk.
Good game.
A little while ago.
Let me in.
Ar, arr...
Oh, no, no, no.
Barrel.
Ah!
Oh, it hurts
Foot pressure point
Don't go in there
Don't go in there!
Ah!
Oh!
I... I... Uh, I'm...
I'm sorry.
I'm tired.
It's fun.
You're the only one here who understands how fun this is.
It's stuck. It's stuck.
This? My throat is...
I'm parched.
Hey, I'm parched.
On your marks. All right, let's go!
Let's go!
So cute!
Mie's fast now.
Fast!
Wow!
That was...
Great job, good job.
You're kind of spooky.
How was your day?
It's been a day. I feel like...
I think I'm gonna have a good dream today.
You know, I can sleep off my meds better than usual.
How was it? Mie.
You know what?
I want to do more.
See you. Let's keep it going.
Let's keep going.
I want to. I want to.
Let's start with the bash.
I went to buy a bash.
Okay, next.
I went to the store to buy a bash.
I'll buy you... a pair of shorts...
Everybody's wearing different colors
I went to the store to buy some bashes.
I went to the store to buy some bashes Bash I went to buy a bash
I went to buy a bash.
Okay, let's do this.
Let's all get a little bit of that.
Let's do it again.
We'll do it again.
Please look forward to it. Please wait for me.
Basketball
Please subscribe to our channel and give us a rating.
See you later.